abeka.com 2017-06-06

# Abeka Academy | Privacy Policy

Abeka.com is operated by _Abeka, Inc._ (“Abeka”), an affiliate of [Pensacola Christian College](http://www.pcci.edu/) (“PCC”). 

We respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. We summarize below the basic information policies and practices in place on the ABeka.com website and related applications. 

Last Updated: November 27, 2013 

##### Information we may collect

We may collect information that can identify you (“personal information”), such as your name and e-mail address, (i) when you (or other users) provide it to us, or (ii) from other PCC affiliates. We may combine the personal information that we receive from different sources.

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our website:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users’ movements around our site and understand trends.
  * We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience.
  * We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should we ever do so, we will comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.

##### How we may use information we collect

We may use information to:

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services;
  * Offer products and services that may be of interest to you;
  * Provide address information and individual shopping interests to select companies whose products or services may be of interest to you;
  * Send you catalogs or other promotional materials on behalf of other companies;
  * Process payment for products or services you order;
  * Customize the content you see on our website;
  * Facilitate use of our website;
  * Manage your account and your preferences;
  * Analyze use of and improve our website, products and services;
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our website; and
  * Enforce any EULA, terms of use, terms of service or other terms/policies governing your use of Abeka products and services.

##### With whom we may share information we collect

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below. We may share personal information with:

  * Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf;
  * Other PCC affiliates;
  * Other select companies whose products or services may be of interest to you; and
  * Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users.

We may share aggregated, non-personal information.

We may allow third-party companies, including AddThis, Google, DoubleClick, and HotJar, to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website in part to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. We may use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

##### Your choices

You may choose:

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain products or services;
  * To stop receiving promotional e-mails or newsletters from us by sending an e-mail to the contact address listed in the promotional e-mail;
  * To delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our website may not function properly;
  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us or, if you have an online account on our website, by logging into that account.

##### Security

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy. Please revisit this site periodically to view the current version of our Privacy Policy.

### Connect With Us

Sign up to get info about helpful features, special savings, & more, or find us on Facebook or Instagram.

Start by selecting your schooling method   
At Home  At School
